jinapdf.com 2018-01-21

# Jinapdf.com Privacy Policy

**Jinapdf.com Privacy Policy**

Last updated: 12th September, 2015.

**Introduction**

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which [www.jinapdf.com](http://www.jinapdf.com/) (“Jinapdf.com”, “Jinapdf” or “Site”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses personal information. We respect your privacy and do not gather any personal data from you that you do not provide voluntarily. We adhere to the applicable privacy laws and always respect your privacy. 

**Application**

This Privacy Policy applies to the Site [www.jinapdf.com](http://www.jinapdf.com/) and to all of the Site’s associated services. It should be read in combination with our _Terms of Use_ and both documents together control the relationship between you and us.

**Who is responsible for personal information collected on the Site?**

The Jinapdf.com Webmaster is the Site owner and operator, and is responsible for the Site’s processing of your personal data and may be contacted using the Site’s [Contact Form](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php). 

**What is personal information?**

Personal information means any information relating to a natural person who is, or can be, identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to the individual. 

**Cookies**

We do use cookies on the Site and if you do not consent to this you should either not use the Site or configure your browser to reject cookies. Cookies are small data files that your web browser places on your computer or device. You may change your browser settings to opt out of cookies but this may prevent the Site from functioning correctly. 

**Protection of minors**

This Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 years and we do not intentionally collect, store or in any way use personal information from children younger than 13 years. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, please contact us using our [Contact Form](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php). In cases where you have authorized a minor (someone under 18 years of age) to use the Site or Services, you acknowledge and agree that you are fully responsible for: 

  * the online conduct of such minor

  * controlling the minor's access to and use of the Site or Services; and 

  * the consequences of any misuse by the minor.

**What personal information do we collect?**

We only collect personal information you voluntarily provide to us. We collect the following personal information:

  * Our [Contact Form](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php) is configured to collect your name and email address. 

  * Through your use of the Site we may also collect your IP address.

  * We may also collect your personal information if you provide it to us through what you write in our contact form or in an email.

**How do we collect personal information?**

We collect personal information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to when you fill out our web contact form or send us an email. 

**If you choose not to provide personal information**

You always have the choice to not provide us with your personal information. It is usually possible to make full use of the Site without providing us with your personal information.

**How we use personal information**

We may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * Provide you with services such as converting your documents to and from PDF form, but note that most use of this service does NOT require you to submit any personal information to us;

  * To improve customer service: For example, where your contact information helps us to respond to your customer service requests and support your needs more efficiently;

  * To improve the Site: For example, we may use feedback you provide to improve the functionality and performance of the Site; and

  * To send emails with general information about Site related special offers and promotions, or other Site news and updates. 

We do not share your personal information with any third parties, expect to the extent necessary to assist you in relation to a purpose listed above. We will never sell or rent your personal information. 

**Non-personal information**

We may collect non-personal information about visitors whenever they interact with the Site. This is mainly in the form of aggregated and anonymous data. This non-personal information may include information on Site visitors such as the type of browsers and operating systems used to access the Site, search terms and search engines used, time spent on various Site pages and other similar information. 

**Google and Xiti Analytics**

This website makes use of Google Analytics. Google Analytics is Google’s analytics tool that helps website and app owners to understand how their visitors engage with their properties. Google Analytics may receive and record information from cookies, server logs, and similar technology from your browser or mobile device, including your IP address. This is controlled by Google as a third party and is not under our direct control. [Learn more about Analytics cookies and privacy information.](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) We may also make use of other analytics tools or services from time to time, for example Xiti.com. 

**Security**

The Site uses appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. 

**Retention of personal information**

Your personal information will be retained for as long as it is needed to operate your account and to meet the requirements of business record retention requirements. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent personal identification information to third parties. We may use third party service providers in association with the Site, for example Google for AdSense advertising and website analytics. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission by agreeing to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to share your personal information in the future if it becomes necessary to do so in order for us to fulfill a legitimate business purpose but will only do so where the third party concerned has agreed to protect such information with appropriate privacy practices that conforming with applicable privacy laws. 

**Personal information you disclose when using the Site**

The Site allows you to send us messages through a [Contact Us](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php) web form. We cannot control your choice to disclose personal information through this form when using the Site and if you do so voluntarily you are consenting to the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Information you upload to the Site for conversion**

Jinapdf.com does not retain any files submitted to the Site for conversion. Files submitted for conversion (either from or to PDF format) are deleted from our servers so your privacy is protected. 

**Links**

This Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party websites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of websites that collect personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on [www.jinapdf.com](http://www.jinapdf.com/). 

**Social Media**

If you use the Site in conjunction with your social media accounts (for example Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter) you are sharing information with those sites, and the information you share will be governed by their privacy policies. You may also be able to modify your privacy settings with these third party social media websites. 

**Cross-border disclosure of your information**

The Site is operated in France. If you are located outside of France, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to France. By using the Site, or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

Your use constitutes acceptance. This means that by using the Site you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**Amendments to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy and/or in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you of these changes by republishing this policy. We recommend you consult this Privacy Policy regularly. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Accessing, updating or correcting your personal information**

You may request access, updates and corrections to any personal information we hold about you at any time by managing it yourself through your account’s administration functions for updating your profile or by contacting us through the Site’s [Contact Form](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php). Where we hold information that you are entitled to access, we will try to provide you with suitable means of accessing it. We will not charge for simply making the request and will not charge for making any corrections to your personal information. 

There may be instances where we cannot grant you access to the personal information we hold. For example, we may need to refuse access if granting access would interfere with the privacy of others or if it would result in a breach of confidentiality. If that happens, we will give you written reasons for any refusal.

**Users who do not want emails from us**

If you do not wish to receive email from us you should not provide your email address and not use the Site. Please note that we do not send unsolicited emails or share your email address with third parties for direct marketing purposes. We may need to terminate your access to some or all content or services to you if we cannot communicate with you by email.

**Release of Personal Information for legal reasons**

We may release your personal information for legal reasons:

  * When we believe in good faith that such release is appropriate to comply with the law (for example, pursuant to a statutory demand, subpoena, warrant or court order).

  * To protect against fraudulent, abusive or unlawful use of the website.

  * To protect our rights or property.

  * If we reasonably believe that a situation involving danger of death or injury to any person requires disclosure.

**Feedback to us**

We have feedback functionality on the Site that allows you to submit comments, suggestions, or bugs found. We may collect your name and email address in order to follow up with you or thank you for a suggestion. 

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, please contact us using the Site’s [Contact Form](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php). 

**Change of Site ownership**

In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all user information to a separate entity. In this event, we will notify its users when user information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Improving this Privacy Policy**

We welcome your suggestions on how to improve this Privacy Policy. Please [contact us](http://www.jinapdf.com/contact.php) through the Site if you wish to provide such suggestions. 

**This document was last updated on 12** **th** **September 2015 and is the most up to date version of our Privacy Policy.**
